Guide to the Margaret Strickland Papers 1880-1963 MSS.077
Fales Library and Special Collections
Margaret Strickland Papers
1880 - 1963
Fales Library and Special Collections
Worley, Richard Hugh
Strickland, Margaret, d.1970
MSS.077
5.09 Linear Feet (10 Containers)
The Margaret Strickland Papers feature the original typescripts of the English writer's biographical works, novels, plays, short stories, and short non-fiction pieces. In addition, this collection includes correspondence, diaries, hand-assembled illustrated magazines, photographs, and scrapbooks, dating from the 1880s to early 1960s.
Provenance
The collection was purchased from James Burmester in 1996.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Biographical Note
Margaret Strickland (circa 1880 - 1970) was a prolific English writer of magazine stories and novels for adults and children. She was the author of the Michael Gerahty detective books for children, and appears to have been reasonably well known as a writer, as this collection documents interest in her work abroad. Margaret was married to Richard Hugh Worley, elder son of R.J. Worley of Essex, by Reverent A. Dawson Clark at St. Andrew's Westminster on October 19, 1908.
Margaret had two sisters, both noted for their ability in drawing animals and staid, country scenes. Agnes Strickland is still remembered for her botanical illustrations, and Diana Mary (later Mrs. Mallet Veale) moved to Rhodesia and became well known for her illustrations of native life. Margaret's grandfather Thomas Strickland was the youngest brother of Agnes, Jane and Elizabeth Strickland, and Catharine Parr Traill. Agnes was the best known of the family and is remembered for her monumental work, The Lives of the Queens of England (1840-1848). Several of Thomas' siblings, including Catharine and another brother, Samuel, immigrated to Canada, where Catherine wrote a number of books and novels, and Samuel founded the city of Lakeside.
Scope and Content Note
The Margaret Strickland Papers document Strickland's professional and personal life, and include original typescripts of her biographical works, novels, plays, short stories, and short non-fiction pieces. These reveal a variety of interests; while she often published adult romance stories of the middle and upper classes that incorporate mystery or suspense, she also wrote the children's detective novel Michael Gerahty (1936), which garnered interest from the film industry. Her children's stories reflect her love of animals, often featuring animals with human characteristics.
Strickland's diaries, ephemera, and scrapbooks reveal her interest in crossword puzzles and gardening. This collection also includes photography of home life, friends, and family, including snapshots of architecture, domestic interior design, gardens, pocket portraits and postcards of loved ones, and group portraits featuring her husband Richard Hugh Worley's childhood and education at the University of Cambridge. In addition, Strickland's personal correspondence comprises over 146 letters (over 660 pages) from Strickland’s sweetheart “Louis”, as well as letters from her husband while he was on active service with the British Expeditionary Force and Kings Royal Rifle Corps during World War I.
Some of the most notable items in the collection are the twelve issues of "Illustrated Amateur Magazine," a small homemade publication Margaret created with her sisters Agnes, Diana Mary, and their friends in Bromley, Kent [now London], from 1897 - 1899. Despite their adolescent origins, these issues of "Illustrated Amateur Magazine" feature an especially acute knowledge of the publishing industry of the period, articles about current culture trends, and refined artwork in the form of original ink drawings and watercolor paintings.
Arrangement
Collection materials have been arranged into five series: I: Correspondence, II: Manuscripts, III: "Illustrated Amateur Magazine," IV: Diaries, Ephemera, Scrapbooks, and V: Photographs. Series II: Manuscripts represent the most substantial portion of the collection and house four different subseries: A: Biographical, B: Novels, C: Plays, and D: Short Fiction & Non-Fiction. Materials are arranged alphabetically by their provided title or subject category, and then chronologically if applicable. If a record is not physically dated, approximate ranges are provided.
Separated Material
There is no information about materials that are associated by provenance to the described materials that have been physically separated or removed.
Typescripts.; Diaries; Scrapbooks.; Illustrations.; Watercolors (paintings); Juvenilia.; Notes.; Drawings; Drawing, English |y 19th century.; Clippings (information artifacts); Photographs; Women authors, English.; Women |x Fiction.; Personal papers.; English fiction |y 19th century.; Women novelists.; Writings (document genre); Short stories |z England |y 19th century.; Manuscripts for publication.; England |v Juvenile fiction.; Correspondence.; Portraits.; Pulp literature.; Strickland, Agnes, 1796-1874; Strickland, Margaret, d.1970
- Series I: Correspondence
  Arrangement
  These materials are arranged alphabetically by the name of the individual in contact with Strickland or the subject in conversation. In the case that a record includes more than one date expression, the listing will begin with its earliest. If a record is physically undated, approximate ranges are provided. These records are noted "undated" and followed by a "circa" estimate determined by the range represented in the same series.
  Scope and Contents
  Series I: Correspondence pertains to Margaret Strickland’s personal and professional life, including correspondence from her closest friends, family, and colleagues in the publishing industry. This series features over 146 letters (over 660 pages) from Strickland’s sweetheart “Louis”, in addition to letters from her husband Richard Hugh Worley while he was on active service with the British Expeditionary Force and Kings Royal Rifle Corps during World War I.
  English fiction |y 20th century.; Women authors, English.; Authors, English |x Correspondence.; Authors, English |y 20th century |v Correspondence.; Personal correspondence.; Personal papers.; Commercial correspondence.; Manitoba, Canada; World War, 1914-1918 -- Correspondence.; Kent, England; London, England.
  - [Assorted Personal Correspondence], 1900 July 6; 1901 July 22; 1923 August 21; 1952 December 31 & July 27 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    6 Letters, 4 Envelopes with Postage & Seal, 1 Post Office Telegraph Form
    Addressed To: “Miss [Margaret] Strickland, Holmdale, Bromley, Kent, [England]”; “Mrs. [Margaret Strickland] Worley, 88 Alderney Street, Victoria, SW1 [London, England],” “Cornwall, Brentwood, Essex, [England]”
    Sent From: “Alfred P. Bushell, Mackie’s House, Sedbergh, [Yorkshire, England]”; “Carolyn J. Strickland, 3 Alexander Street, New Brunswick, NJ, USA”; “Gwyneth Beare of Reydon Hall, Southwold, Suffolk, [England], Wangford 247”; “Royal Horticultural Society, Vincent Square, SW1, [London, England]”; [Unidentified Party of Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada]
    In Reference To: Family / Friendship / Genealogy / History / Personal; “Biographical Record of Arthur B. Strickland” Request for “The National American Cyclopedia of American Biography, James T. White & Company, 101 Fifth Avenue, New York, NY”; “Businesses Associated with Debenhams Limited” List, Sir Thomas Strickland, Sizergh Castle
    24 Pages, Unbound
    Typed, Printed & Handwritten in Ink & Pencil
    Measurements: 4.75” x 3.5” - 8” x 13”
  - [Assorted Professional Correspondence], 1910 January 14 - 1924 January 25 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    6 Letters, 1 Envelope with Notation & Postage
    Addressed To: “Miss Margaret Strickland, 88 Alderney Street, [Victoria, London, England]”
    Sent From: “Bas (Possibly Brother), 22 Market Street, King Lane Tom. CP”; “Dr. Robert N. Gordon, O Company, No. 1 Convalescent Camp, Boulogne, France”; “Mrs. E. Peterson, 2 Ladbroke Road, Notting Hill Gate, London W11, [England]”; “P. Habberton Lutham, The Odd Corner, Hurstpierpoint, Sussex, [England]”; “P.W. Everett, The Novel Magazine of C. Arthur Pearson Limited, Henrietta Street, London WC [England], Telegrams ‘Humoursome, London’ & Telephone 7927 & 7928 Gerrard”; “W.O. Bayer, Film Department of Curtis Brown, Limited, International Publishing Bureau, 6 Henrietta Street, Covent Garden, London, WC2, [England]"
    In Reference To: Business / Professional / Writing; Bill Adams, “Elusive Peg,” “Flirtations of Phyllis,” “The Way of the Serpent”; “Tales of Temptation,” “Tiger’s Eyes” “The Sword (Blue Magazine)”; “The Doom of Fate,” “Porch of Wrong”; United States Serial Rights
    12 Pages, Unbound
    Measurements: 6” x 2.5” - 8" x 10"
  - "Louis": Kent & London, England, 1901 June 25; [no year] October 8; undated, circa 1901 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    76 Letters, 1 Envelope with Postage
    Addressed To: “Miss [Margaret] Strickland, Holmdale, Tweedy Road, Bromley, [Kent, England]”
    Sent From: “Louis, Langham Hotel, London, [England],” “Huonville, Shortlands Road, Shortlands, Kent, [England], Telephone 146 Bromley,” “Timperley, Northdown Avenue, Margate, [Kent, England]”
    In Reference To: Friendship / Personal; “Hugo Gorlitz, Musical & Dramatic Agency, 119 New Bond Street, London West [England]”; Musical Notation; Poetry
    Approximately 300 Pages, Unbound
    Measurements: 4.5” x 4.5” - 8” x 10.5”
  - "Louis": Kent & London, England; Wiesbaden, Germany, [no year] May 20; undated, circa 1901 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    38 Letters
    Addressed To: [Miss Margaret Strickland, Holmdale, Tweedy Road, Bromley, Kent, England]
    Sent From: “Louis, Huonville, Shortlands Road, Shortlands, Kent, [England], Telephone 146 Bromley,” “Timperley, Northdown Avenue, Margate, [Kent, England],” "Villa Beatrice, Gartenstrabe 12, Wiesbaden, Germany”
    In Reference To: Friendship / Personal; “Hugo Gorlitz, Musical & Dramatic Agency, 119 New Bond Street, London West [England]”; “Keogh-Wright Private Hospital, 166 West 2nd North Street, Salt Lake City, UT, Telephone 409”; Poetry
    Approximately 200 Pages, Unbound
    Measurements: 4” x 6” - 8” x 10.5”
  - "Louis" with Cobham Grant: Barrow-In-Furness, Kent & Lancashire, England, 1895 January 31; 1901 March 27; undated, circa 1895 - 1901 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    32 Letters, 2 Envelopes with Postage
    Addressed To: “Miss Margaret Strickland, Holmdale, Tweedy Road, Bromley, Kent, [England]”
    Sent From: “Cobham Grant, Lonsdale, Guildford Road, Tunbridge Wells, [Kent, England],” “Louis, Holt’s Commercial Hotel, Haslingden, [Rossendale, Lancashire, England],” “Huonville, Shortlands Road, Shortlands, Kent, [England], Telephone 146 Bromley,” “Imperial Hotel, Barrow-In-Furness, [England] with Proprietor E. Bowden, Telephone 87,” “℅ Mrs. Wood, Timperley, Northdown Avenue, Margate, [Kent, England]”
    In Reference To: Friendship / Personal; National Provincial Bank in Piccadilly; Poetry; Royal College of Music
    Approximately 160 Pages, Unbound
    Typed, Printed & Handwritten in Ink
    Measurements: 4.75” x 3.75” - 8” x 10.5”
  - Worley, Richard Hugh: Manitoba, Saskatchewan, & Winnipeg, Canada; Winchester, England, 1910 March 11 - 1923 November 25 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    12 Letters
    Addressed To: [Margaret Strickland]
    Sent From: [Richard Hugh Worley, Husband of Margaret Strickland] “℅ Thomas Acheson, CPR Agriculturalist Agent, Winnipeg, [Canada]” “From [Rifleman C6198 Worley, 12th Kings Royal Rifle Corps, On Active Service with the British Expeditionary Force, YMCA,” “Kings Royal Rifle Depot, Winchester, [Hampshire, England],” “Moose Jaw, Saskatchewan, Canada,” “St. Claude Hotel, St. Claude, Manitoba, Canada”
    In Reference To: Family / Marriage / Military / Personal / Political / World War I
    Approximately 65 Pages, Unbound
    Handwritten in Ink & Pencil
    Measurements: 4.75” x 6” - 6.25” x 10”
- Series II: Manuscripts
  These materials are arranged alphabetically by title or subject, then chronologically if applicable. In the case that a record includes more than one date expression, the listing will begin with its earliest. If a record is physically undated, approximate ranges are provided. These records are noted "undated" and followed by a "circa" estimate determined by the range represented in the same series and or subseries.
  Scope and Content
  Series II: Manuscripts documents Strickland's professional writing in the form of original typescript drafts with handwritten editing notation of over sixty-two titles, separated into four different subseries: A: Biographical, B: Novels, C: Plays, and D: Short Fiction & Non-Fiction. The final subseries, D: Short Fiction & Non-Fiction features small collections of Strickland's published work. "Five Animal Short Stories" [Box 4, Folder 20] and "Twelve Uncanny Stories" [Box 6, Folder 2] are handmade portfolio booklets of Strickland's stories that were published in The Blue Magazine & The Red Magazine, The Violet Magazine, and The Yellow Magazine, which were part of a small British popular fiction pulp format separated by subject and printed by the Amalgamated Press between July 1922 and December 1929. This series also comprises drafts of writing in various genres including adult mystery and romance fiction, children's adventure and detective fiction, historical fiction and creative non-fiction, as well as tests about animal care, food recipes and home remedy instructions.
  Booklets.; Rhodesia, Africa.; Animal Stories.; Creative nonfiction.; Marginalia (annotations); Plays (document genre); Women |x Novels.; Young Adult Fiction, English; London, England.; Notes.; English fiction.; English drama |y 20th century.; Newspapers.; Typescripts.; Manuscripts for publication.; Manuscripts (document genre); Manuscript preparation (Authorship).; Manuscripts |x Editing.; Women novelists.; Novels.; Novelists, English |y 19th century.; Novelists, English |y 20th century.; Commercial correspondence.; Recipes.; Formulas, recipes, etc.; Romantic Fiction.; Pulp Literature, English; Children's Literature, English; Articles.; Feature articles.
  - Subseries A: Biographical
    - "He Sought Not Fame" Chapters I - XIV, undated, circa 1908 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      1 Manuscript with Introduction, Notation, & Preface
      “He Sought Not Fame, And Fame Did Overlook His Unobtrusive Merit: Being the Life of Captain Thomas Strickland, (E.I.N.S.) & Brother of Trinity House, Born 1812, Died 1877” by His Granddaughter, Margaret Strickland, 88 Alderney Street, [Victoria, London, England] SW1”
      149 Pages, Bound by String
      Typed & Handwritten in Ink & Pencil
      Measurements: 8”x 10”
    - "He Sought Not Fame" Chapters XV-XXXVII, undated, circa 1908 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      1 Manuscript with Notation
      113 Pages, Bound by String
    - "He Sought Not Fame" [Manuscript in Full], undated, circa 1908 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      1 Manuscript with Handpainted Strickland Family Crest, Introduction, Notation & Preface
      “He Sought Not Fame, And Fame Did Overlook His Unobtrusive Merit: Being the Life of Captain Thomas Strickland, (E.I.N.S.) & Brother of Trinity House, Born 1812, Died 1877” by His Granddaughter, Margaret Strickland, 88 Alderney Street, [Victoria, London] SW1 [England]”
      323 Pages, Unbound
      Typed & Handwritten in Ink
    - "History and Genealogical Notes of the Strickland Family", 1893; 1895 January 28 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      3 Manuscripts with Notation
      “History and Genealogical Notes of the Strickland Family” by Catherine (Catharine) Parr Traill (née Strickland) of Westove, Lakefield, Ontario, Canada [2 Copies; Notation from Samuel C. Strickland of St. Paul, MN]
      “Further Notes of Family Interest” by Margaret Worley (née Strickland)
      30 Pages, Bound & Unbound
      Measurements: 8”x 12.5”
      Catharine Parr Traill (January 9, 1802 – August 28, 1899) was an English-Canadian author and naturalist who wrote children's and settler literature. Traill was the last surviving member of the Suffolk, England Stricklands. Many of Traill’s albums of plant collections are housed in the National Herbarium of Canada at the Canadian Museum of Nature in Ottawa, Ontario.
  - Subseries B: Novels
    - "Called Away" Chapters I - XI, undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      1 Manuscript with List of Contents & Notation
      “By Margaret Strickland, 88 Alderney Street, [Victoria, London, England] SW1, Telephone Victoria 3287”
      123 Pages, Bound by String
      Measurements: 8” x 3.75” - 8” x 10”
    - “Called Away” Chapters XII - XX, undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      [By Margaret Strickland, 88 Alderney Street, Victoria, London, England SW1, Telephone Victoria 3287]
      106 Pages, Bound
      Measurements: 8” x 10”
    - "Called Away" Manuscript Cover, undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      “A Novel by Margaret Strickland”
      Typescript Mounted on Brown Tissue with Ribbon
      Measurements: 9.5” x 11"
    - "[A] Michael Gerahty 'Case' ", undated, circa 1908 - 1936 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      1 Manuscript with Index, Notation & Black Cover
      “A Book for Boys and Girls of 10 to 16 Years By Margaret Strickland, 88 Alderney Street, [Victoria, London, England] SW1, Telephone Victoria 3287”
      281 Pages, Bound & Unbound
      Typed, Handpainted & Handwritten in Ink
    - "[A] Michael Gerahty 'Case' " Chapters XX - XXI, undated, circa 1908 - 1936 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Manuscript Fragments of Alternative Version with Notation & Yellow Back Cover
      ["A Book for Boys and Girls of 10 to 16 Years," By Margaret Strickland, 88 Alderney Street Victoria, London, England SW1, Telephone Victoria 3287]
      27 Pages, Bound by String
      Typed & Handwritten in Pencil
      Measurements: 8” x 10.75”
    - "Michael Gerahty, Detective or The Ogre's Den", undated, circa 1908 - 1936 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      1 Manuscript Synopsis with Notation & Back Cover
      “A Book for Boys & Girls from 10 to 15 Years, Published By Eyre & Spottiswoode, [Written] By Margaret Strickland, 88 Alderney Street, [Victoria, London, England] SW1, Telephone Victoria 3287”
      23 Pages, Unbound
      Measurements: 8” x 3” - 8” x 13”
    - "Michael Gerahty, Detective" Royalty Statement, 1936 December 12 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      1 Financial Record Fragment
      Addressed To: “Miss Margaret Strickland, 88 Alderney Street, [Victoria, London, England] SW1”
      Sent From: “Eyre & Spottiswoode Publishers Limited, 6 Great New Street, London, [England] EC4”
      In Reference To: Business / Children’s Literature / Professional / Writing
      1 Page, Unbound
      Printed & Handwritten in Pencil
      Measurements: 7.75” x 3.75”
    - "The Crouching Shadow", undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      1 Manuscript with Notation & Yellow Cover
      “By Margaret Strickland, 88 Alderney Street [Victoria, London, England] SW1, Telephone Victoria 3287”
      200 Pages, Bound by String
      Measurements: 9” x 11”
    - "The Mystery of Curling Water" Chapters I - XIX, undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      1 Manuscript with Illustration, Index & Notation
      “By Margaret Strickland, 88 Alderney Street, Victoria, London, [England] SW1, Telephone Victoria 3287”
      224 Pages, Bound by String
    - "The Mystery of Curling Water" Chapters XX - XXXIII, undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      151 Pages, Bound & Unbound
    - "The Mystery of Curling Water" Manuscript Cover, undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Typescript Mounted on Brown Cardboard
      Handwritten in Ink
      Measurements: 8” x 10.5”
    - "The Personality of Flowers", undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      1 Manuscript with Blue Cover & Notation
      “By Margaret Strickland, F.R.H.S [Fellow of the Royal Horticultural Society], 88 Alderney Street, Victoria, London, [England] SW1, [Telephone Victoria 3287]”
      158 Pages, Unbound
    - "The Wildenhall Story" Chapters I - XVIII, undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      “By Margaret Strickland, F.R.H.S [Fellow of the Royal Horticultural Society], 88 Alderney Street, Victoria, London, [England] SW1, Telephone Victoria 3287”
      201 Pages, Bound by String
    - "The Wildenhall Story" Chapters XIX - XLIV, undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      253 Pages, Bound & Unbound
    - "The Wildenhall Story" Chapters XLV - LXIX, undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      [By Margaret Strickland, F.R.H.S [Fellow of the Royal Horticultural Society], 88 Alderney Street, Victoria, London, England SW1, Telephone Victoria 3287]
      260 Pages, Bound & Unbound
    - "The Wildenhall Story" Correspondence, undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      1 Letter
      Addressed To: “To Whom it May Concern”
      Sent From: “Margaret Strickland” [F.R.H.S, Fellow of the Royal Horticultural Society, 88 Alderney Street, Victoria, London, England SW1, Telephone Victoria 3287]
      In Reference To: Business / Children’s Literature / Professional / Writing; “I apologize for the bulk of this manuscript and realize it is far too long”
    - [Unidentified]: "Part II", undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      1 Manuscript with Notation & Yellow Back Cover
      59 Pages, Bound & Unbound
  - Subseries C: Plays
    - "A Case for Divorce", undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      “A Play In One Act By Margaret Strickland, 88 Alderney Street, Victoria, [London, England] SW1, [Telephone Victoria 3287]”
    - "A Pair of Gloves", undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      1 Manuscript with Correspondence - Ephemera, Illustration & Notation
      “A Play In One Act By Margaret Strickland, 88 Alderney Street, Victoria, London, [England] SW1, Telephone Victoria 3287”
      Sent From: “Curtis Brown Limited, 6 Henrietta Street, Covent Garden, London, [England] WC2”
      In Reference To: Business / Professional / Writing; Production Sketch; “Tit-Bits Novels - Every Monday” Newsprint Clipping with Notation
      29 Pages, Unbound
      Measurements: 7” x 9.5” - 8” x 10”
    - "The Case of Lottie Bursall", undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      1 Manuscript with Illustration & Notation
      “By Margaret Strickland, 88 Alderney Street, Victoria, London, [England], SW1, Telephone Victoria 3287”
      22 Pages, Unbound
    - "The Strife of Tongues", undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      4 Manuscripts with Character & Scene List, Notation
      “A Play In Four Acts By Laurence Therval & Margaret Strickland, From the Novel By Margaret Strickland, 88 Alderney Street, Victoria, London, [England] SW1, Telephone Victoria 3287”
      87 Pages, Unbound
      Measurements: 8.5” x 11”
    - "The Strife of Tongues" Manuscript Cover, undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      “By Margaret Strickland, 88 Alderney Street, Victoria, London, [England] SW1, [Telephone Victoria 3287]”
      Typescript Mounted on Blue Cover
  - Subseries D: Short Fiction & Non-Fiction
    - "A Brief for the Cat" [2 Copies], undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      2 Manuscripts with Notation
      “By Margaret Strickland, ℅ Mrs. Mallet Veale [Diana Mary Strickland], Reydon, Gadzema, South Rhodesia, [Africa]; 88 Alderney Street, Victoria, [London, England] SW1”
      11 Pages, Unbound
    - "A Brief for the 'Common Cold' ", undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      “By Margaret Strickland, 88 Alderney Street, Victoria, [London, England] SW1”
      3 Pages, Unbound
    - "A Question of Colour", undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      1 Manuscript
      [By Margaret Strickland, 88 Alderney Street, Victoria, London, England SW1]
      5 Pages, Unbound & Typed
      Measurements: 7.75” x 9.75”
    - "Aspidistra", undated, circa 1908 - 1940 (Box 4, Folder 9)